**EXPERIENCE** 

2017-present **Google** Sales Engineer, Google Cloud

> 2014-2016 **Sencha Inc.** Sales Engineer, EMEA

> Customer facing work:

BMW, CERN, Thales, FinancialForce.com

Public speaker:

FITC, Devoxx, Apps World, SenchaCon, O'Reilly

> 2012-2014 Lead Technical Trainer, EMEA

> > Trained customers:

EMC, Nielsen, Deloitte, McAfee, NASDAQ

> 2009-2012 **eFocus**

Lead Front-end Developer Teamlead of a team of 5

Customer facing work:

Heineken, Amstel, Philips, Estee Lauder Deloitte, Friesland Campina, Miele

2007-2009
Accenture
Senior Java Developer
Worked as a consultant for:
KLM / Air France, KPN, UPC

2004-present **Ladysign** Founder

Website & app development:

VVD, BMG Germany

Book author: O'Reilly Media

**EDUCATION** 

2004-2008 • Saxion Enschede Bachelor, Art & Technology (graduated July 2008)

Activities and Societies: Functional/Technical Design, Arts & Design, UML, Java, Web & Mobile Technologies



## Lee Boonstra, Overtoom 310-1 1054 JD Amsterdam NL

+31 6 51536814 | me@leeboonstra.com June 16th 1983 (Apeldoorn NL) | Dutch | Female http://www.leeboonstra.com | http://nl.linkedin.com/in/leeboonstra

**SUMMARY** 

Currently working as a sales engineer for Google in the Google Cloud team. I provide pre-sales technical assistance to our customers, prospects and internally to our sales, engineering and marketing teams. It also involves developer evangelism. I speak at conferences, organize meetups & seminars and I write technical documentation & prototypes.

Experience in leading teams, working with customers, public speaking, organizing events, technical writing, training and (mobile) web app development for the enterprise.

TECH SKILLS

GOOGLE CLOUD, GSUITE, CLOUD COMPUTING DATA ANALYSIS, MACHINE LEARNING NODE JS, PYTHON, DJANGO, PHP, JAVA SQL, NOSQL, MONGODB, MYSQL, FIREBASE DOCKER, KUBERNETES, GIT, SVN OSX, WINDOWS, UNIX, ANDROID, IO RESTFUL WEBSERVICES, JSON, XML

JAVASCRIPT, ES2015, ANGULAR2
JQUERY, DOJO, MOOTOOLS
HTML5, SASS, CSS3
PHONEGAP/CORDOVA, ELECTRON
SALESFORCE CRM & APIS
MVC, MVVM, OOP, UML
AGILE, SCRUM, JIRA

EXT.JS. SENCHA TOUCH

## **LANGUAGES**

- Dutch (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- German (Basic)
- **OTHER**

• Book Author: Hands-on Sencha Touch 2: A real world app approach

(O'Reilly Media: ISBN-10: 144936652X- July 2014) http://www.amazon.com/Hands-Sencha-Touch-Real-World-Approach/dp/144936652X

- Magazine Author: .NET Magazine #247: Sencha Tutorial: How to build a mobile utility app (Future Plc Oct 2013)
- Book Reviewer: Sencha Touch Mobile JavaScript framework (Packt: ISBN: 1849515107 Feb 2012)